JENNY LONG



647-719-8878





<u>ienny.long@ryerson.ca</u> (in Linkedin.com/in/jenny-long

PROFILE

A highly responsible and attentive computer science student with 4.5+ years of customer service experience which enabled strong conflict resolution, problem solving and communication skills. Seeking to acquire an internship or research opportunity to further develop my abilities in the field of computer science.

EDUCATION

B.Sc. Computer Science Candidate (Expected graduation May 2023) Ryerson, Toronto, ON

B.A (Hons) Psychology May 2017 York University, Toronto, ON

SKILLS

Languages

- Java
- Python
- HTML

Operating Systems

- MacOS
- Windows

Technical - Extras

- MS Office Suite
- **SPSS**

Developer Tools

- **VS** Code
- **Eclipse**
- Spyder

Spoken Languages

- English (native)
- Cantonese (conversational)

CERTIFICATIONS

- **Smart Serve**
- **Applied Suicide Intervention** Skills Training

PROJECTS

Student Registry Simulator

Feb 2020 - Apr 2020

- Developed a student registry simulator that creates active courses, enrolls students to courses, drop courses, sets grades, and a scheduler which prints the students schedule.
- Built using java, implementing array lists, objects, classes, file and exception handling, inheritance, interfaces, comparator and comparables.

Cross Word Puzzle Game

Nov 2019 - Dec 2019

Developed a 20 by 20 crossword puzzle game by implementing two dimensional arrays, loops and comparisons using Python.

Poker Hand Recognition

Oct 2019 - Nov 2019

- Developed a program that evaluates and identifies the type of poker hand by the 10-character string hand.
- Built using Python, implementing Boolean primitive data types, loops, functions and if statements

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

KEY HOLDER

DalyCarol Fashion | Toronto, ON | Oct 2015 – Aug 2019

- Interacted with approximately 30 customers daily, building strong customer base by providing personalized product recommendations, resolving issues and following up on products.
- Succeeded in increasing weekly sales by 10% while accomplishing a high level of customer service
- Assisted with calculating the store's end of year inventory.

SUPERVISOR

Jugo Juice | Vaughan, ON | Oct 2014 – Sept 2015

- Opened and closed store according to company policy and guidelines
- Assisted and trained new associates in all cash register responsibilities including cash balancing, handling customer purchases and organizing cash register.
- Established strong rapport with regular customers and employees with an optimistic and engaging attitude.
- Investigated and resolved customer inquiries and complaints in a timely and empathetic manner.